That was what mattered.
Fort as the phase down into a pit to protect itself.
They shot through the camp.
So you couldn't go, you had to crawl in the ditches,
Because it small everywhere.
And some ridges looked like Tesils.
It was terrible.
I never thought I would experience it.
Because it was
an incredible fire at the camp
And all around.
You thought
Survive!
So this goes to the forest.
There came tanks that turned the tower toward us
And towards the camp.
I see and hear it in front of me now,
screams, cries,
And gunfire.
So I backed back as much as I could.
So he pushed himself up in front of me.
Just as he came up, he sank down again.
So I got hold of him like this.
I thought he just fainted
But then I saw that he was bleeding.
He had received a shot in his right eye.
Which went in and stopped four centimeters from the back of the head.
I told Rune once
that you saved my life.
Hadn't you stood there
Then it was calm and peaceful.
“Swedish UN soldiers go by mail
at the multi -hundred -year -old fortifications. ”
"As today should be only tourist attractions."
“But that still matters,
just like fortifications. ”
The Turks were not allowed to be on the wall
in Old City.
Because then the Greeks shot and threw grenades.
So we would remove them there.
Then I got as a mission
to become the head of that strength.
We were a group that loaded a KP car
and would make a temporary observation site up there.
Then I told my driver: Don't stop for anything.
If there is a roadblock.
Drive through!
We're going up there now.
Then a lot of soldiers came up.
Turkish Cypriots.
They were of course cursed.
But then came Mûnûr.
So he and I
stood opposite each other.
With each weapon.
I was snooped but not afraid.
I thought he couldn't shoot me.
Then I told Mr.
Mûnûr that you know what applies.
You may not be up here,
You have to take away your guys and go down.
But then when it got dark, at midnight.